(Penny:)Why are you yelling at me?
(Leonard:)Sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Never mind, we're cool.
(Penny:)Dave is not smarter than you.
He's an idiot.
(Leonard:)Really? Why would you say that?
(Penny:)Because a smart guy takes the nude photos
of his wife off his cell phone...
(Penny:)...before he tries to take nude photos
of his girlfriend.
(Leonard:)He tried to take nude photos of you?
(Penny:)That's what you took from that?
(Penny:)The guy is married.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah.
I'm sor... Oh, that's terrible.
(Penny:)And you. If you are so okay with the way
things are between us, why are you jealous?
(Penny:)Well, that...
(Leonard:)The important thing is
he's married and that's terrible.
(Penny:)Nice save, genius.
(Penny:)- Eggnog?
- Lactose.
(Penny:)It's just rum. It stopped being eggnog,
like, a half an hour ago.